<?xml version="1.0"?>
<lockit>
	<_1 value="Bee" />
	<_2 value="Cat" />
	<_3 value="Cow" />
	<_4 value="White Shepherd" />
	<_5 value="Mallard" />
	<_6 value="Goat" />
	<_7 value="Horse" />
	<_8 value="Sheep" />
	<_9 value="Snail" />
	<_10 value="Squirell" />
	<_11 value="Owl" />
	<_12 value="Mouse" />
	<_13 value="Fox" />
	<_14 value="Penguin" />
	<_15 value="Polar bear" />
	<_16 value="Walrus" />
	<_17 value="Wolf" />
	<_18 value="Seal" />
	<_19 value="Snowy Owl" />
	<_20 value="Dolphin" />
	<_21 value="Octopus" />
	<_22 value="Fish" />
	<_23 value="Humpback whale" />
	<_24 value="Shark" />
	<_25 value="Elephant" />
	<_26 value="Giraffe" />
	<_27 value="Wildebeest" />
	<_28 value="Leopard" />
	<_29 value="Black Rhino" />
	<_30 value="Zebra" />
	<_31 value="Lion" />
	<_32 value="Yak" />
	<_33 value="Tiger" />
	<_34 value="King cobra" />
	<_35 value="Indian peafowl" />
	<_36 value="Panda" />
	<_37 value="Proboscis monkey" />
	<_38 value="Parakeet" />
	<_39 value="Saltwater Crocodile" />
	<_40 value="Kangaroo" />
	<_41 value="Kiwi" />
	<_42 value="Koala" />
	<_43 value="Emu" />
	<_44 value="Platypus" />
	<_45 value="Green sea turtle" />
	<_46 value="Dingo" />
	<_47 value="Congratulation!" />
	<_48 value="OK" />
	<_49 value="PLAY" />
	<_50 value="Choose your animal." />
	<_51 value="Upon this, the seamen rushed to the yard-arms, as in swarming-time the bees rush to the boughs. Bare-headed in the sultry sun, Ahab stood on the bowsprit, and with one hand pushed far behind in readiness to wave his orders to the helmsman, cast his eager glance in the direction indicated aloft by the outstretched motionless arm of Daggoo." />
	<_52 value="Mammal" />
	<_53 value="Tigers are so powerful, roar! However only less than 10% of hunts end successfully for them." />
    <_54 value="Reptile" />
    <_55 value="Bird" />
    <_56 value="Insect" />
    <_57 value="Mollusc" />
    <_58 value="Fish" />
	<_59 value="Proboscis monkeys are excellent swimmers and have partially webbed feet. Look at my nose! - Said Proboscis Monkey." />
	<_60 value="King Cobra may kill an elephant with a single bite. On the other hand its venom is used in painkillers" />
    <_61 value="An elephant's trunk is used for breathing, trumpeting, drinking, smelling, grabbing things. What a handy nose, isn't it?" />
    <_62 value="An elephant's trunk is used for breathing, trumpeting, drinking, smelling, grabbing things. What a handy nose, isn't it?" />
    <_63 value="Did you know that actually the males are known as peacocks, whereas  the females as peahens?" />
    <_64 value="Parakeets can learn to speek. Rolling in the deep, wet grass... A parakeet sings while taking a shower." />
    <_65 value="Bamboo here, bamboo there -Yummy. Pandas eat almost only bamboo." />
    <_66 value="Domesticated Yak is really appreciated due to its milk, meat, fur and ... dung (which is used as a fuel)!" />
    <_67 value="Who does smell like cough drops, sleep up 18h a day and is adorable? A koala!" />    
    <_68 value="Emu is omnivorous, it eats both plants and small animals, emu does even swallow small rocks to accelerate digestion." />
    <_69 value="Hop, hop, kangaroo is the largest animal that use hoping as the primary mode of locomotion." /> 
    <_70 value="Kiwi- a cute, furry ball, known to be the only bird to have external nostrils at the end of its long beak. You may even hear it sniffing." /> 
    <_71 value="Funny looking animal- with a beak, a venom spur and it lays its eggs. The platypus is a very strange creature." /> 
    <_72 value="Sadly, lots of baby turtles die just after hatching- during their run to the sea." /> 
    <_73 value="Despite being a dog, dingo cannot bark. Instead it howls like a wolf- awhooo!" /> 
    <_74 value="This species is known for its ability to swim far out at sea. Beware!" /> 
   <_75 value="Goats are very curious-they chew odds and ends just to find out more about these objects- they can even eat something like a tin can." />
   <_76 value="Just one ounce og honey will be sufficient o fuel a bee's tavel around the world." />
   <_77 value="This breed emerged from white-coat lines of the German Shepherd. Isn't it adorable?" />
   <_78 value="A snail may feed on materials rich in calcium (e.g. soil or rocks) in order to preserve its shell as hard as possible." />
   <_79 value="The red squirrel puts exess food into caches, and very often it forgets where are they." />
   <_80 value="Mooooo! Moooooo! No milk today!" />
   <_81 value="Did you know- female mouse is named doe, male one is a buck and the babies are called pinkies!" />
   <_82 value="Sheep are known to eat specific plants when ill in order to be cured." />
   <_83 value="Horses have almost 360 degree vision- except the blind spot directly in front and behind them." />
   <_84 value="Anatidaephobia- a person suffering this condition feels that somwhere in the world a duck is watching her." />
   <_85 value="Cats are true sleepheads-they sleep 70% of their lives." />
   <_86 value="Lions very often work together to prey upon the large animals. The cooperation is the key to success!" />
   <_87 value="Each zebra's stripes are as unique as fingerptints, there are no two exactly alike." />
   <_88 value="The same material you can find in your hair- keratin is also the main component of a rhino's horn." />
   <_89 value="Agility- leopards run up to 58km/h, can leap 6m horizontally and 3m vertically, they are also very elusive." />   
   <_90 value="The wildebeest follow the rains in order to find the food>  They travel 1000 miles as year." />
   <_91 value="Giraffes are the tallest mammals, they spend up to two hour asleep a day." /> 
   <_92 value="Octopuses have the ability of changing their body shape to mimic other animals." />
   <_93 value="Dolphins use echolocation to prey and navigate. Besides, they are very playful animals." />
   <_94 value="Humpbacks love breaching, acrobatics and singing, their songs can be heard up to 20 miles away." />
   <_95 value="Sharks can 'feel' electrical field thank to a sensory organ - ampullae of Lorenzini." />
   <_96 value="There are over 30000 known species of fish." />
   <_97 value="There is no land based predators in Antarctica therefore this funny animals present no particular fear of humans." />
   <_98 value="A polar bear's skin is actually black, this color soaks up the sun's heat and helps stay a bear warm." />
   <_99 value="Wolf pups like to play a lot- chasing, wrestling, playing hide-and-seek, just like all children." />
   <_100 value="Snowy owls have excellent eyesight and hearing which help them to prey upon lemmings." />
   <_101 value="Foxes habe whiskers no only on ther face but also on their legs, which help them to navigate in darkness." />
   <_102 value="Walrus whiskers are called vibrissae. Vibrissae are used to help them locate food at the bottom of the ocean." />
   <_103 value="Harp seal milk contains so much fat, so pups gain over 2.2 kilograms per day!" />
   <_104 value="Lifespan" />
   <_105 value="years" /> 
   <_106 value="Weight" />
   <_107 value="kg" />
   <_108 value="Class" />
   <_109 value="" />
   <_110 value="" />
   <_111 value="" />
</lockit>